marriedbutlonely.com 2013-10-13

# marriedbutlonely.com - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**   
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITES OR SERVICES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.  
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITES OR SERVICES.

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

We understand and respect the privacy concerns of our users. Therefore, we have made it a critical focus to protect the confidentiality and security of the personal information you provide us.   
This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices of marriedbutlonely.com and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively “Company”, “we”, “us”, or “our” ) and governs the use of the website, or other Company products and services (collectively, the “Services”)by users of the Services (“you” or “your” ).We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you about what information we collect, how we use and share your information, and our privacy practices. 

**The Information We Collect**

In order for our services to work and work economically, we need to obtain certain information from our users. We may collect two types of information: Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) and Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII).  
PII is information that identifies a specific user of the Services and is provided by the user. When you engage in certain activities on the Services, such as when you register to use the Services, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself that we will collect and store. Depending on what activity you are engaged in, some of the information that we request will be identified as mandatory or as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular activity, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity.  
We may also collect demographic data for certain Services, which helps tailor the Services to display content that we think would provide the greatest benefit to the user. You do not have to engage in the activities in which we ask you to provide such information. But if you choose to do so, we may ask you to provide information, such as your first and last name, gender, email address or date of birth.  
Our applications do not enable GPS location automatically, however, if you access the Services via a mobile device, then the PII may also include user location information if your device provides GPS/location services and you turn those features on to benefit from our applications functionalities. This information may reveal your actual location, including GPS data. Non-PII is information that identifies your computer and its navigational patterns through the Services (but not a specific user). We may automatically collect Non-PII information when you visit the Services, through the use of a variety of tools including cookies (small text files that are stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes and which contain information about that user’s computer), or other available data analysis or collection technologies. 

**How We Use and Share Information**

We use the information we collect to (a) provide, maintain, and protect the Services; (b) notify you of promotions, special events, new services and special offers, for example, through e-mails; (c) tailor our product offerings, customer service and overall experience; (d) improve the content, operation, appearance and utility of the Services; (e) conduct surveys, research and evaluations; (f) troubleshoot and resolve disputes; (g) gather demographic data and (h) accomplish other administrative tasks.  
If you decide that you are no longer interested in receiving email communications from us, you may follow the instructions in our emails to unsubscribe from our email list or by emailing us at support@contactusonline.com.  
We may share your information collected on the Services with our subsidiaries and other affiliated companies, and with other trusted vendors and business partners. Such business partners include companies who provide business services to us or on our behalf, such as to market products or services to you, monitor Services activity, serve Services content, help to maintain our customer database, administer e-mails, surveys or other contests, and fulfill orders [if applicable].  
We also reserve the right to disclose your information in good faith as required by law, in response to legal process including law enforcement requests, and with any person or entity that may acquire all or any part of our business or assets, in connection with any change in control of us, and where needed to prevent fraud and to protect the safety, property, or legal rights of users of the Services or our affiliates.

**Unsubscribe, Opt Out or Revoke**

You may revoke consent at any time for any use of PII, including user location information, collected from you under this Privacy Policy. To revoke consent, indicate by emailing us at support@contactusonline.com with the word “revoke Personal Information” in the subject line.

**Privacy Policies of Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy only addresses the Services offered by us. Other websites or services, such as those websites we provide links to, websites or services you may have clicked-on that directed you to the Services or websites that may be accessible to you through the Services, have their own privacy policies regarding data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you visit any such website, we encourage you to review that website or service’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

**Editing and Requesting Your Information**

We will permit you to change your profile settings. Even after you remove your information from your profile, copies of your information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others or it was copied or stored by other users. We may also be required to retain your information by law or for legitimate business purposes, such as to prevent identity theft or other misconduct.  
We will permit you to request a copy of your PII that we have collected about you by emailing us at support@contactusonline.com. You can also correct factual inaccuracies in this information by emailing us at support@contactusonline.com.

**Storage and Security**

We will retain PII, including user location information, only as long as our business needs require. We will then destroy or render unreadable any such information upon disposal.  
We believe the security of your information is a serious issue and we are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We use commercially reasonable security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your information under our control. Notwithstanding such measures, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or 100% secure, and we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Services. We also are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information. 

**European Union**

We comply with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of data from the European Union and Switzerland, respectively. Information regarding both the E.U. and Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks can be found at: [export.gov/safeharbor.](http://export.gov/safeharbor)

**Minors and Privacy Issues**

Use of the Services and access to the websites are restricted to persons over the age of 18. No part of the Services is designed to attract anyone under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect or maintain information from anyone known by us to be under the age of 13.   
If you are a parent or guardian and believe that your child under the age of 18 has provided personal information to us and/or is accessing the Services, please contact us to request this information and the account will be deleted.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. The revised Privacy Policy will be effective immediately when posted on the Services. It is the responsibility of each user to review the Services and the Privacy Policy to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Services after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. If a change would authorize the use of your PII for a new or materially different purpose, then we will send you an email notification.

**Contact Information**

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or to report abuse of any PII collected under this Privacy Policy, please email us at support@contactusonline.com with the word “Privacy Policy” in the subject line, or contact us at support@contactusonline.com. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).
